export const javascript = [
  {
    quiz_name: "JavaScript Arrays Quiz",
    quiz_id: 2,
    category_id: 2,
    category_name: "javascript",
    questions: [
      {
        questionId: 1,
        question: "What does the method .length do in an array?",
        choices: {
          A: "Adds a new element to the array",
          B: "Returns the number of elements in the array",
          C: "Removes the last element from the array",
          D: "Creates a new array",
        },
        correctAnswer: "B",
        chosenAnswer: "",
      },
      {
        questionId: 2,
        question:
          "How do you access the first element of an array called 'arr'?",
        choices: {
          A: "arr{0}",
          B: "arr.first()",
          C: "arr(0)",
          D: "arr[0]",
        },
        correctAnswer: "D",
        chosenAnswer: "",
      },
      {
        questionId: 3,
        question: "What does the method .length do in an array?",
        choices: {
          A: "Returns the number of elements in the array",
          B: "Adds a new element to the array",
          C: "Removes the last element from the array",
          D: "Creates a new array",
        },
        correctAnswer: "A",
        chosenAnswer: "",
      },
      {
        questionId: 4,
        question:
          "How do you access the first element of an array called 'arr'?",
        choices: { A: "arr[0]", B: "arr.first()", C: "arr(0)", D: "arr{0}" },
        correctAnswer: "A",
        chosenAnswer: "",
      },
      {
        questionId: 5,
        question: "What does the method .length do in an array?",
        choices: {
          A: "Returns the number of elements in the array",
          B: "Adds a new element to the array",
          C: "Removes the last element from the array",
          D: "Creates a new array",
        },
        correctAnswer: "A",
        chosenAnswer: "",
      },
      {
        questionId: 6,
        question:
          "How do you access the first element of an array called 'arr'?",
        choices: { A: "arr[0]", B: "arr.first()", C: "arr(0)", D: "arr{0}" },
        correctAnswer: "A",
        chosenAnswer: "",
      },
      {
        questionId: 7,
        question: "What does the method .length do in an array?",
        choices: {
          A: "Returns the number of elements in the array",
          B: "Adds a new element to the array",
          C: "Removes the last element from the array",
          D: "Creates a new array",
        },
        correctAnswer: "A",
        chosenAnswer: "",
      },
      {
        questionId: 8,
        question:
          "How do you access the first element of an array called 'arr'?",
        choices: { A: "arr[0]", B: "arr.first()", C: "arr(0)", D: "arr{0}" },
        correctAnswer: "A",
        chosenAnswer: "",
      },
      {
        questionId: 9,
        question: "What does the method .length do in an array?",
        choices: {
          A: "Returns the number of elements in the array",
          B: "Adds a new element to the array",
          C: "Removes the last element from the array",
          D: "Creates a new array",
        },
        correctAnswer: "A",
        chosenAnswer: "",
      },
      {
        questionId: 10,
        question:
          " How do you access the first element of an array called 'arr'?",
        choices: { A: "arr[0]", B: "arr.first()", C: "arr(0)", D: "arr{0}" },
        correctAnswer: "A",
        chosenAnswer: "",
      },
    ],
  },
];
